export const linux: QuizData[] = [
  {
    quiz_name: "Linux Commands",
    quiz_id: 10001,
    questions: [
      {
        questionId: 1,
        question: "What does the 'ls' command do?",
        choices: {
          A: "Moves a file",
          B: "Creates a new directory",
          C: "Deletes a file",
          D: "Lists directory contents",
        },
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        questionId: 2,
        question: "What does the 'pwd' command do?",
        choices: {
          A: "Prints files to the screen",
          B: "Deletes a file",
          C: "Displays the current working directory",
          D: "Creates a new directory",
        },
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        questionId: 3,
        question: "What does the 'cd' command do?",
        choices: {
          A: "Lists directory contents",
          B: "Changes the current directory",
          C: "Deletes a directory",
          D: "Copies a file",
        },
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        questionId: 4,
        question: "What does the 'mkdir' command do?",
        choices: {
          A: "Moves a file",
          B: "Copies a file",
          C: "Creates a new directory",
          D: "Deletes a directory",
        },
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        questionId: 5,
        question: "What does the 'rm' command do?",
        choices: {
          A: "Deletes a file",
          B: "Renames a file",
          C: "Lists directory contents",
          D: "Moves a file",
        },
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        questionId: 6,
        question: "What does the 'cp' command do?",
        choices: {
          A: "Copies files or directories",
          B: "Changes directory",
          C: "Lists directory contents",
          D: "Renames a file",
        },
        correctAnswer: "A",
      },
      {
        questionId: 7,
        question: "What does the 'mv' command do?",
        choices: {
          A: "Creates a directory",
          B: "Moves or renames a file",
          C: "Deletes a file",
          D: "Changes the current directory",
        },
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
      {
        questionId: 8,
        question: "What does the 'cat' command do?",
        choices: {
          A: "Copies a file",
          B: "Lists file sizes",
          C: "Concatenates and displays file content",
          D: "Deletes a file",
        },
        correctAnswer: "C",
      },
      {
        questionId: 9,
        question: "What does the 'echo' command do?",
        choices: {
          A: "Lists directories",
          B: "Renames a file",
          C: "Deletes a file",
          D: "Outputs the strings that are passed to it",
        },
        correctAnswer: "D",
      },
      {
        questionId: 10,
        question: "What does the 'man' command do?",
        choices: {
          A: "Changes directory",
          B: "Displays the manual for a command",
          C: "Deletes a file",
          D: "Creates a new file",
        },
        correctAnswer: "B",
      },
    ],
  },
];
